UCLA University Archives. Moving image and audio recordings. ca.1940- UARC.0642
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Frances Clarke Sayers - Storytelling session at the home of Carolyn Horovitz, UES librarian., 1975 Jun 07.; 5 in., magnetic tape. (Box 14)
- Dedication - Medical School Laying of the cornerstone 1951; and Academic Freedom - Loyalty Oath - Meeting on the quad Fitzgerald, Neff and Westergaard 1950., 5 in., magnetic tape. (Box 14)
- CASO - morning and afternoon sessions and panel discussions., 1973 Jun 09.; 5 in. magnetic tape, 3 tapes. (Box 14)
- Bandini - "Weed Out" & "Two Way Super Plush", KNX Editorial (?)., 1972 Mar 016.; 5 in., magnetic tape. (Box 14)
- Association for Jewish Studies - Religion in a Religious Age, Speros Vyronis, MorDechai Friedman, Herbert Davidson, Moshe Perlmann, Shelomo Goitein and Arnold Band., 5 in. magnetic tape, 3 tapes. (Box 14)
- Friends of the Library - Jack Smith and John Weaver dialogue, Page Ackerman introduction., 1976 Dec 08.; 5 in. magnetic tape. (Box 14)
- Page Ackerman - transcript of reply to KNX Editorial Broadcast., 1973 May 10. (Box 14)
  contents confirmed 2013 Mar 014
- Lecture - Ewing Lectures, Katherine Anne Porter, "Two Lectures on Mark Twain"., 1959 Oct 07 and 09.; 7 in. and 10" in. magnetic tape, 3 tapes. (Box 15)
- Royce Hall., n.d.; 11 in., music mastering tape. (Box 15)
  labeled "master", contents confirmed 2013 Mar 014 jej
- Card Stunts, 1967 (Box 16)
  Film 10 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_016_001
- Alumni Day, 1961 (Box 16)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_016_002
- Crew - San Diego, 1973; Film 12 in. (Box 16)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_016_003
- Anniversary Awards - Film Clips, 1962; Film 10 inch (Box 17)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_017_001
- Ethnomusicology - A World of Music, n.d.; Film 10 inch (Box 17)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_017_002
- Education is Everybody's Business, 1960; Film 11 inch (Box 18, Reel 1)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_018_001
- UCLA - The Future is Now, 1988; 2 Reels; Films Marked "revised 5/88, backup, scratches at end" and "revised 6/88" (Box 18, Reel 2-3)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_018_002 and _003
- Homecoming, 1957; 16mm film 12 inch (Box 19)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_019_001
- Perceptual Motor Evaluation of a Perceptually Normal Child, n.d.; 16mm film 12 inch (Box 19)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_019_002
- University of California - Which Campus?, n.d.; 16mm film 12 inch (Box 19)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_019_003
- Card Stunts, 1959-1960; 16mm film 14 inch (Box 20)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_020_001
- Card Stunts and Band at the Rose Bowl, 1961; 16mm film 14 inch (Box 20)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_020_002
- Homecoming, 1958; 16mm film 14 inch (Box 20)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_020_003
- UCLA - 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1979 September 16; 16mm film 14 inch (Box 21)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_021_003
- Homecoming, 1945; 16mm color film 14 inch (Box 21)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_021_002
- Golf - ASUCLA Golf Day, n.d.; 16mm film 14 inch (Box 21)
  This film has been digitized: uars_642_021_001
- UCLA - Nuclear Medicine and Radiation Biology Laboratory Cornerstone Ceremony, 1960 May 21 (Box 22)
  16mm film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_022_003
- Card Stunts, Nite [Night] Card Stunts and Band, 1948-1953 (Box 22)
  16mm film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_022_001
- Homecoming, 1955; 16mm film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_023_001 (Box 23)
  contents confirmed 2013 Apr 1 jej
- Homecoming Olympic Daze, 1956; 16mm film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_023_002 (Box 23)
- Homecoming UCLA - Stanford, 1954; 16mm film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_023_003 (Box 23)
- Card Stunts and Light Stunts, 1956; Film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_024_001 (Box 24)
- Card Stunts in Light and Sound, 1957-1958; 16mm film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_024_002 (Box 24)
- Card Stunts, includes 1954 Rose Bowl appearance stunts, 1954-1955; 16mm color film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_024_003 (Box 24)
- Homecoming, 1951; 16mm film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_025_001 (Box 25)
- Homecoming, 1952; 16mm film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_025_002 (Box 25)
- Homecoming, 1953; 16mm film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_025_003 (Box 25)
- UCLA - A Bruin Named Joe, 1953; 16mm color film 12 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_026_001 (Box 26)
- UCLA - Jackie Robinson Baseball Field, 1981; 16mm film 11 in. This film has been digitized:uars_642_026_002 (Box 26)
- UCLA - KTTV Campus Cameo "UCLA Campus", 1966; 16mm film 11 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_026_003 (Box 26)
- UCLA Medical Center - California Medical Television Network, n.d.; 16mm film 10 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_027_001 (Box 27)
- American Heart Association - Eddie's Miracle, n.d.; 16 mm film 11 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_027_002 (Box 27)
- UCLA Medical Center - Epilepsy, 1979 January 01; 16mm film 11 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_027_003 (Box 27)
- Fernald School - The Tutors of Fernald, n.d.; 16mm film 12 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_028_001 (Box 28)
  contents confirmed 2013 Mar 28 jej
- Card Stunts, 1968; 16mm film 12 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_028_002 (Box 28)
- Card Stunts and Rose Bowl, 1965; 16mm film 12 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_028_003 (Box 28)
- UCLA - A Westside Story, includes footage of most UCLA campus buildings and aerial views, Chancellor Franklin Murphy, Chancellor Charles Young and students, 16mm sound and color film 12 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_029_001 (Box 29)
  Frank E. Hobden, producer, Barbara Searles, writer, contents confirmed 2013 Apr 4
- UCLA - Charter Day, "The Day Two Presidents Came to UCLA," President Lyndon Baines Johnson, President Aldolfo Lopez Mateos (Mexico), President Clark Kerr, Chancellor Franklin D. Murphy. Helicopter arrival, campus motorcade, convocation and hooding, 1964 February 21; 16mm silent color film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_029_002 (Box 29)
  see box 12 for audio, Stan Troutman cinematographer, contents confirmed 2013 Apr 4
- UCLA - Research, 50th anniversary documentary produced for KNBC. Includes Frederick D. Abraham, Derwyn M. Severy, Yoshio Setoguchi, Margaret H. Jones, Ellen Andersen, Paul Terasaki, Peter Kamnitzer, Awtar Singh, 1969 December; 16mm sound and color film 12 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_029_003 (Box 29)
  Rod Serling, narrator, Abe Wollock, Theater Arts department, producer, contents confirmed 2013 Apr 4
- Homecoming, 1947; 16mm color film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_030__001 (Box 30)
- Homecoming, 1948; 16mm film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_030_002 (Box 30)
- UCLA Story - US Information Service Presents UCLA, n.d.; 16mm sound film 14 in. This film has been digitized: uars_642_030_003 (Box 30)
- Westwood Village Dedication, 16mm film and 2 DVD copies, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Unidentified 16mm Agfa film, H.N. Beimfohr, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Japanese Evacuation, UCLA Senior Night and Unknown Event, 16mm film, H.N. Beimfohr, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- UCLA 1944 Graduation; "Susie Q"; Fall Retreat, 1944 and Winter Retreat, 1945, 16mm film, HN Belmfohr, 1944; 1945 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- UCLA W.F, 1941; UCLA Baccalaureate and Graduation, 1941, Elton and Margaret Wedding, 1941, 16mm film, HN Beimfohr (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Gluck, Sherna, "The Practice of Women's Oral History," Oral History Conference, 1 cassette, Spring Quarter, Apr. 23, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Sherbakova, Irina, "Women of the Gulag," Oral History Lecture, 1 cassette, Fall Quarter, Oct. 16, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Nash, Gary, Interview on Angela Davis, cassette tape and CD copy (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Grele, Ronald, "What Makes Oral History Different?" Oral History Lecture, 1 cassette, Winter Quarter, Feb. 6, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Hunter, Madeline, Speech to University Affiliates, 5" tape, 1984 Feb 2 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Witherspoon, Blanche, Address to Gold Shield, tape introduced by Bernard Galm; Mrs. Witherspoon introduced by Mary Erickson, 2 copies, 5" tape, 1979 Jan 27 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Lab Circulation Service, S. Hilton, 7" audio reel, Reel 1, 1970 Jun 30 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Lab Circulation Service, S. Hilton, 7" audio reel, Reel 2, 1970 Jun 30 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- UCLA Experience from Students to Alumni, 1 VHS tape, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Ralph Bunche, 1 VHS tape, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 5)